In the battle with Archbishop Orwell,
in which she tried to use Akari's Pure Concept of Time
to regain her youth,
I came in contact with Akari's consciousness
and realized something.
Akari had rewound time back several months
to relive the time she had spent with me.
The reason she was so friendly from the moment we
met was a remnant of what she had already experienced.
That means despite earning so much of Akari's trust,
I somehow failed to kill her.
That's why this time, I'll make sure I kill Akari.
Deep within me,
there's another personality I don't even know about.
It's the true Akari Tokitou,
who remembers everything from before I regressed.
The true me rewound time just so
I could prevent Menou's death.
Don't you die, Menou.
And this time...
Make sure you kill me properly.
"These gates are open to any who wish to pass through."
"Be they healthy, ill, happy, unhappy,
diligent, slothful, wise, foolish..."
"be they devout followers or any kind of heretic,"
"be they pure or evil of heart,"
"these holy gates are open unto them."
It's a quote that represents the spirit of pilgrimage.
I like these words.
They say leaving through these gates and finishing
the journey absolves people of all of their sins,
and that they're reborn anew.
I see they issued you a new scripture, Menou.
Yes. The acting archbishop arranged it for me.
I also got enough travel funds for the time being,
so we can set off without any worries.
Yeah, off we go on a pilgrimage!
...Yes.
Our destination is the Sanctuary.
It's on this pilgrimage route, way off at the very end.
Right.
There's a residential area for Lost Ones
there that can take me in, right?
But even if the trip is smooth it
will still take about three months.
No problem! As long as I'm with you.
Then let's get going.
Oh hey. Wait, Menou.
As long as we're doing this,
let's take the first step together.
Please?
Oh, all right. Sure.
Okay, here we go.
Ready, and...
That's right, this is a fresh new step,
toward finding a way to kill Akari and carrying
out the deed with my very own hands.
Episode 7: Port City of Libelle
Hey, Menou.
This place... Uh, the "wilderness area," was it?
You mean the Wild Frontier?
The environment is so harsh that humans
gave up on pioneering it altogether.
Stretches of it lie in between the countries.
Didn't you say there are scary creatures out here?
The monsters. Yes, there are.
There are also outlaws around who
call themselves "adventurers."
The area seems awfully normal, considering.
This is the pilgrimage route, so it's relatively safe.
But we'll see just how long you're so optimistic.
I'll be just fine! This is gonna be a breeze!
Come on, Menou! Hurry, hurry!
Fine, fine.
Two weeks later
I can't go on anymore!
Like I said, it's only a bit farther.
This is wearing down my soul!
If it was, you wouldn't be saying that.
Well, that's true.
When you're really worn down,
you don't even have the energy to complain.
Then okay!
Want to know why my soul is still fulfilled,
even on such a tough journey?
Not really.
You really do, huh?!
It's because...
You, my emotional oasis-is right by my side.
Meanwhile, I think you're draining me of all of my energy.
Can't you find a more self-sufficient
way to boost your spirits?
I can only get Menou nutrients from the real thing.
I'll shrivel up if I don't get enough!
No you won't.
You lived just fine for sixteen years before you met me!
I have no recollection of those sixteen years anymore.
It's all about today, Menou.
We're young and we should only live in the present.
You should look back on the past and
think about the future at least a little bit.
Look, our future is coming into view.
Wow, it's a town! The ocean's so big! And blue!
It's the Port City of Libelle. It's nice and relaxing.
Ooh, I can't wait!
Look, it's the ocean.
Right.
It's the first time you see it, isn't it?
Yes.
Don't you have anything to say?
It's big.
Is that all?
It's blue.
You really are so emotionless, girl.
Master.
Is that fog?
"Fog," hmm? Technically, not quite.
That's none other than one of the
Four Major Human Errors scattered around the world:
The Pandemonium.
Sealed away in there is a calamity
that almost destroyed the world.
Those who enter can never hope to come out again.
A prison of fog.
Hey.
Do you think those are clouds?
If the weather's going to take a turn,
we should hurry, right?
Don't worry about that.
Really?
Yes...
That thing is always there.
I need to stop by somewhere, so I'm going on ahead.
Wait for me, Menou!
We will be sure to process your request.
I'll be back. Thank you.
Menou! Are you done?
Yes.
But I can't believe you have to apply for travel
funds at a church in every town we come across.
They're providing us with money. I can't complain.
And I guess we get to see the sights as a bonus.
Hey, Menou!
There's somewhere I want to check out!
There! The island with the castle!
Oh, you mean Libelle Island.
Unfortunately, we can't go there.
Why not?
That island is the private property of Count Libelle,
a dignitary of the city.
We can't go unless we're on special business
or there's an event or something.
Aw, I see.
Don't be so discouraged.
There are plenty of other places to see here.
Are you sure?
It was a long two weeks on the road.
Why don't we splurge a bit?
"Splurge"?!
Yeah, yeah! Let's do it!
Let's go then! Come on!
Fine, fine.
Flare's successor, Flarette, hmm?
Yes...
I remember her...
Public bath
This is so nice...
I'm glad you seem to be enjoying this.
Well, the fact that your idea of "splurging"
is the public bath goes to show how strapped
for money you've been, but anyway.
That's not it. It shows I live in honorable poverty.
I know, I know.
You're pure, just, and strong, as a priestess should be.
Hey, Menou.
Our destination on this journey is some
place called "the Sanctuary," right?
That's right.
If I go there, they'll take me in.
But you know, I've been kind of thinking...
It wouldn't be so bad if I kept
traveling around this world...
With you, Menou.
Don't be silly.
The point of a journey is to get to a destination.
I don't know. I like taking side trips, too.
Whatever.
I'm getting out before you.
Go ahead.
Akari will be in there a little while longer.
Okay!
Menou!
Oooh, I haven't seen you in two weeks!
I can feel your warmth. You're mine. All mine!
I don't share you with anyone else, Menou!
Okay, okay. I'm impressed though, Momo.
You traveled the Wild Frontier away from the pilgrimage
route and still managed to get here before us.
It was nothing!
Well, I did get harassed a bit by that
crappy little princess again on the way.
Princess Ashuna?
Why would the princess of Grisarika
come all the way out here?
Who knows?
She probably has a thirst for battle or something.
"A thirst for battle"?
Anyway, I beat her down into the danger zone
of some ancient ruins and left her there.
If I'm lucky, she's already dead.
I see...
Anyway, how long do you intend to stay here in Libelle?
What? Why?
Don't you remember this town is famous
for teeming with those people?
"Those people"...
Oh, do you mean the Fourth?
Yes. Despicable, aren't they?
They insist they're a liberated Fourth class
who aren't Faust or Noblesse or Commons,
yet all they do is engage in random acts of terror.
They don't make any sense.
But they had quite a movement going for a while.
If our Master hadn't captured
their leader a few years ago,
they may have been a threat to the world even now.
Yes, exactly.
I figure the Fourth have a grudge against Master Flare.
Well yes, perhaps.
And you're called Flarette, "Flare's successor," you know?
So I need to be careful.
Yes. Not that I'm too worried about you.
I did look into the Fourth in town just in case,
so I'll send the details to your scripture later.
Thanks, Momo. I'm proud to have such a capable aide.
Well, you have every right to be proud.
More praise, pleeaase!
There, there.
Sounds like Akari's about to come out.
Awww.
Oh, by the way!
Speaking of Boobalicious,
are you not going to try out the Pandemonium?
Otherworlder or not,
she might not be able to escape if you toss her in there.
There might even be some crazy
monster inside that would eat her for us.
Th-that's true.
Don't tell me you hadn't even considered it?
I hadn't. I completely spaced out.
It's definitely more promising than the usual methods.
It may be worth a try.
Sorry to keep you waiting!
That was an awfully long bath, Akari.
This is normal for a Japanese person.
It is?
Hey, Menou. Weren't you just talking to someone?
No, I wasn't.
Come on, Akari. Sit down there.
I'll dry your hair for you.
Okay!
This is just what I was worried about.
Menou isn't sure about killing that girl...
Am I hesitating?
No, that can't be right.
Thank you, Menou.
I'm an Executioner.
And the job of an Executioner...
is to kill Lost Ones.
Libelle is such an interesting place!
The area has lots of hills,
so the buildings were designed to accommodate that.
Yeah!
The title would be, "The Ocean, the Town, and Menou."
Yeah, what a great shot!
Thanks, I guess. I'm glad you're having fun.
Yeah, I'm glad I'm having fun, too!
But it's really too bad we can't go over there.
It's such a lovely castle.
Like I said yesterday, we can't set foot on that island.
But, we can look at it up close from the sea.
I'm sure we could borrow the church's boat.
Want to go?
Really?!
You can steer a boat, Menou?
I'm a pure, just, and strong priestess,
pretty much capable of anything.
Just leave it up to me!
Wahoo! This feels great!
That's dangerous. Will you sit down?
And did you take that nausea medication I gave you?
Oh, that's right.
We're getting closer to the castle!
Did you say it belongs to a count?
Yes.
But, ever since Count Libelle fell ill,
his only daughter has been acting on his behalf.
Apparently she's still in her teens.
Wow... Menou, you really know a lot, huh?
I just heard about it at the church yesterday.
Though it was really from Momo.
That must be tough,
being acting head of a household around my age.
One of the initial members of the Fourth,
Count Libelle also funded their operations.
Now in his place,
the person put in place as the leader of the Fourth in
this city is his daughter, Manon Libelle.
Are we sure she's in town now?
She was spotted on the pilgrimage route.
Considering the timing, she must be.
Why does it have to be the successor of Flare,
the sworn enemy of the Fourth?
Is she strong, this woman?
Rumor has it that she's the one who
took down Archbishop Orwell.
We can't underestimate her.
Lady Manon.
Yes?
Please share your thoughts on behalf of Count Libelle.
Um, why don't we just watch her for a while?
Perhaps she'll simply move on without doing anything.
Honestly, Lady Manon.
Well, perhaps you're too young to know
how much of a threat Flare was-
I do.
My mother was killed by none other than her, after all.
She was a useless woman,
considering the trouble we went through to get her.
In any case, we must do something about Flarette.
Before it affects the distribution of our product.
I'll go and make a preemptive attack.
I assume that's all right with you, Lady Manon?
Yes. I'll be sure to tell my father.
Well, then...
I must take my leave now,
but I hope you will all enjoy the sandwiches.
It would be a shame to throw them out.
She's only a child, after all. We can't count on her.
Well, at least the food she serves tastes good. I'll give her that.
The Pandemonium...
A prison of fog that they say is easy enough to enter,
but impossible to escape from.
Even for Akari,
who can revive herself by regressing time...
This might just work.
I see the drug has taken its effect.
Auto Etheric Connect (Condition: Met) - Improper Attachment
Pure Concept [Time] - Unlock
Where am I?
Oh, right. It's Libelle.
I'm in the Pandemonium, so everything must be on track.
Yup, glad everything's going smoothly.
Whoa, there!
I have to get swallowed by that thing again?
How many times has it been?
It feels awful in there.
But, this place can't kill me.
Sorry, Menou.
What's this light?
This wasn't here the last time...
If Akari dies here, this journey will be over.
After that, nothing changes.
I'll just go back to life as an Executioner.
But, what's this pain I feel in my heart?
Is it guilt?
No, I don't deserve to suffer from that kind of thing.
Ooh, ouch!
Uh, what? Why did I just bump my head?
Wasn't I looking up at the castle?
That's weird.
What are you saying?
After you finished seeing the
castle you said you were sleepy,
and snoozed off like an idiot, remember?
And now you're suddenly up and all confused.
What, really?
Sorry Menou, after the trouble of bringing me here.
It's fine.
Hey, were you actually sad being left alone for a while?
As if!
I was grateful to get a bit of peace and quiet.
Hey, that's mean!
It would be nice to say you were sad,
even if you weren't.
Fine, whatever.
We're going back.
My hair will get damaged from the ocean breeze.
Hey, Menou?
What?
You know why I slept so well?
I think it's because I feel so safe next to you, Menou.
That's true.
The fact that Akari currently revives next
to me is probably because of that.
But by using her Pure Concept,
Akari is another step closer to
letting her power get out of control.
I'm sure we're still okay...
What do you mean, "okay"?
I mean this.
Wait, what?!
It's been bothering me a bit since I saw you in the bath.
I think you're still okay, just barely.
Hey! What do you mean, "just barely"?!
Someone's in a good mood.
Come, this way.
Go ahead.
Whew, I'm quite hungry.
Let's see, what should I eat?
Oh, I know. Perhaps I should go to the market.
Next Episode
Monstrine
Next episode: Monstrine.